

CONTACT ME

719 1st Ave N, Kent WA 98032

raventimbas@gmail.com

(253) 486-5680

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Collaboration
- Conflict Resolution
- Problem Solving
- Flexibility

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front-end

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- AJAX

Back-end

- JSON
- Python
- PHP
- RESTful API
- Working Knowledge in C/C++
- Working Knowledge in OOP and MVC
- Working Knowledge in NodeJS

Databases

- MySQL
- Knowledgeable in MongoDB

Frameworks / Tools

- Laravel
- WordPress
- Github
- Working Knowledge in SourceTree
- Working Knowledge in WooCommerce
- Working Knowledge in Shopify
- Working Knowledge in Codeigniter4
- Working Knowledge in AngularJS
- Working Knowledge in ReactJS

RAVEN D. TIMBAS

WEB DEVELOPER | SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROILE

A Junior Level Web Developer experienced in creating, developing, testing and modifying web applications. Demonstrated ability in identifying and resolving coding issues and delivering projects on time and within budget. Skilled in front-end, back-end, database and various frameworks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

IFormatLogic IT Solutions | September 2022 - September 2023

- Created pages and templates, troubleshot issues, devised workarounds, recommended design modifications and UX enhancements, and discovered or enhanced appropriate plugins to better show material under the supervision of the project manager.
- Customized the existing plugins and themes to improve UI/UX and to manipulate the data in accordance with the requirements of the client.
- Configured and optimized client servers and third-party web hosting to migrate websites, plugins, posts, pages, databases and other business assets as needed.

Full - stack Developer - On the job training

Dunbrae Subic INC. | March 2022- May 2022

- Modifying and testing changes to previously developed programs
- Develop a Web Automation System
- Creating servers and databases for functionality

IT STAFF - On the job training

Grand Pillar International Development INC. | June 2019 - July 2019

- Installed and maintained hardware and software
- components on computer stations and IT equipment
- Provides network troubleshooting and support

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

College: Gordon College

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science | 2018 - 2022

Senior High School: Tapinac Senior High School

Technical Vocational Livelihood – Home Economics | 2016-2018